<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Application</string>
    <string name="Story_Title_1">THE STORY OF A PRISONER</string>
    <string name="Story_Title_2">THE LIFE</string>
    <string name="Story_Title_3">THE LAST PAGE</string>
    <string name="Story_Title_4">MY ANTHEM</string>
    <string name="Story_Title_5">JUST WAITING</string>
    <string name="Story_Body_1">I am a retired jail warden. As soon as you have read the word jail, your mind must be hovering around the thick high stone walls, people clad in spoiled white clothes having a unique number, and prisoners who were spending their life within an other world. These are in fact true. But, as a person having worked there, I knew their lives at a closer dimension.\nI have seen many people. Most of them ended up in jail because they lacked a minute’s patience. A fight with wife, a brawl with neighbours, a quarrel with relatives claimed the top positions in the list of reasons. Else, they are humans. Humans who lost the essence of their lives in a spurt of minute’s anger. As I got acquainted with them more and more, I came to learn many of them were gifted with a wide spectrum of talents. There were people who have a high scale of academics, who are gifted with the talents of singing etc. There was an another section of prisoners who were scapegoats of others’ faults. We know this very well, thanks to the cine media.The life in the prison leaves dark scars on their future life too because, I consider the society can never accept a person from jail. Forever a tag of prisoner remains in their pasts overcasting their present and future too. Jail is the only place for them where they can remain themselves. To conclude the life inside the walls, I say, it is a whole different world, where people get a chance to repent and to experience renaissance. Of all them whom I have remembered, there was a this man.His name is Ravi.\nRavi came to jail when he was 22. The age where the blood in veins gushes out at the sight that shakes the soul. The age where everyone tries to carve their life out of their dreams and hard work. But, as the fate plays its own game, he landed in jail. Since the day he came Ravi never talked to anyone. He used to be in his own world. He promptly did the work assigned to him, how hard it might turn out to be. He never complained on anything, nor shared his past to anyone. Everyone in the jail found him to be weird for the first few days, but later they got accustomed to his silence. They tried to talk to him, tease him, but failed to make him talk. At last, they concluded that he was dumb, although I never agreed to it.\nI did futile attempts to make him talk, tried to make him reveal his past quite a couple of times. It appeared to me as if he is punishing himself.  I decided not to disturb him. Days went on. Years rolled by. A few of the inmates were released and many others joined . The world changed. Everything changed except for Ravi. He remained the same silent man.
Fourteen years. He spent absolutely fourteen years in the jail. On the year of his release, I dared to talk to him once.He was sitting under the tree. He was alone.\n“Ravi”, I called him, not clear on what to talk to him.\nHe stood up and folded his hands in a respectable manner, and waited as a servent awaiting for his boss orders.\n“Can I have a minute with you?”\nHe looked little dazed but nodded his head in a manner of approval.\nHe looked little dazed but nodded his head in a manner of approval.
“Ravi, this is your final year. Later you may return to your world. In this fourteen years, no one ever saw you talking. I have a strong instinct that you did nothing wrong. Even if you have done something grave causing you to lead your life here, I wish you did to save someone.”</string>
    <string name="Story_body_2">    I never gave much thought to decide which part of life is the best one to describe life. The stage of birth, a growth from a child to an adult, a transition from an incomplete person to a perfect human, the ultimate renunciation are the four stages in any human life.</string>
    <string name="Story_body_3">    It was more than three days since my grandmother had been admitted into the hospital. I was staying with her all the time. The doctor’s said that her position was helpless. Aged more than 65, she has always been my mentor, guide, teacher and my best friend. We have a very special bond woven by the threads of love and understanding. I don’t remember a moment where the signs of age disheartened her playful spirit. She is revered and respected by all the members of our family not only for being the oldest but for being the wisest and also for the love and care she showed. Her husband, my grandfather, passed a few years back. Since then, she had been living with my family. Not even in my worst nightmares, I dreamt that such a situation would arise where she would be fighting for every breath to live. Tears flowed from my eyes day and night.  My dad was helpless too. My mom appeared calm but I can understand that she is too shaken to even let her tears out. I lost appetite. Though mom and dad did shifts for being in the hospital, since they need to be with our relatives at my home, I was only person who was constantly sitting in the same chair, in front of the same room, with my unstoppable tears flowing down my swollen eyes. I sat praying to all the gods I know  to let her be with us a few more years, at least till my marriage gets done.</string>
    <string name="Story_body_4">    When you can’t hear the silence of your silence,\n
When you can’t feel your souls’ presence,\n
When you are unable to hear your hearts’ deepest moan,\n
When you are left all alone,\n
When your mind is in its’ darkest hour,\n
When your eyes are witnessing your worst nightmare,
\nWhen your ears can’t hear your cries,
When your path is no more visible,\n
When your destiny is hidden by the illusions of your fear,\n
It is the time my heart.\n
The perfect time.\n
To be born once again.\n
To learn once again.</string>
    <string name="Story_body_5">He opened the door of his room. And he entered into his world, a world which knows who he is, what he is and why he is. He sat on his bed with his back facing the window which stood as a confluence point of fading rays of the setting sun and cool breeze of the calm evening. Aged more than fifty five, he has rough but curly salt and pepper hair, a moustache which isn’t trimmed properly. His eyes are sunk into the sockets safeguarding them, indicating the number of sleepless nights he has spent in search of her memories. He looked around the room. Everything is in its position for absolutely thirty two years. Not even inch did they move, nor did he tried to move them, for she liked it the way they were and how they are. Slowly he opened the chest of drawers ,to let her memories possess him, to let her memories love him once more, to let her memories leave some more memories to make him live for some more days.</string>
    <string name="Story_1_date">Posted on June 28, 2016</string>
    <string name="Story_2_date">Posted on May 23, 2016</string>
    <string name="Story_3_date">Posted on May 18, 2016</string>
    <string name="Story_4_date">Posted on March 22, 2016</string>
    <string name="Story_5_date">Posted on March 10, 2016</string>
</resources>
